https://www.carnifest.com/privacy-policy/

Most Visited
New York City London Paris Barcelona Berlin Munich Madrid Amsterdam Sydney Canberra
Most Visited
New York City London Paris Barcelona Berlin Munich Madrid Amsterdam Sydney Canberra
BUY
TICKETS
Concert Sport Theater & Comedy Gift cards
AboutContact Us
CarniFest Online respects absolutely the privacy of every person visiting our website.
CarniFest Online will not collect any personal information about you (i.e., your name, address, telephone number, or email address), unless you provide it to us voluntarily.
Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. We will NOT make your personal information available to any person, persons or companies for any reason whatsoever.
The only ways we can obtain your personal information is if you send us a general enquiry or feedback.
If you do not want your personal information collected, please do not submit it to us!
When you do provide us with personally-identifiable information, we will only use that information to improve the purposes of CarniFest Online website provide, or to contact you regarding CarniFest Online matters which we think you may be interested in.
In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally-identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using, and the domain name of the website from which you linked to our site. This information is used to compile standard statistics on site usage.
This site contains links to other sites and to third-party vendors that may serve. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content at the end of those links, but we make our link choices only after careful consideration of their potential impact on our visitors.
Important:
Our site users may opt out of cookies (if the other sites or vendor offers this capability).
Google Advertising Cookie and Privacy Policies:
• Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
• Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the       Internet.
• Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Our website uses cookies in order to give you a better user experience, by continuing to use our website, you agree to the use of cookies as described in our cookies policy.
